sixfigureprogram.com 2011-11-25

# Privacy Policy | Six Figure Program

### Privacy Policy

We may collect your personal information but only if you voluntarily provide your personal information such as email address, name, address, phone number. We may collect your name and email address to provide you with a free gift such as our “Success Blueprint”, a free DVD, free video, etc. You will receive such a free gift via email or by way of "snail mail" if we designate same. You may also receive similar emails with other material. You may opt-out of our email list anytime you like. We are can-spam compliant. You can click the unsubscribe link in any email. Or, just send us an email asking us to opt-out which you can send to: ben@sixfigureprogram.com or dave@sixfigureprogram.com.

**Order Information**

Customers may use an order form to purchase our products. When you place an order, we collect contact information, such as your shipping and e-mail addresses, and financial information, such as your account or credit card numbers. Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and information to our customers and to get in touch with them when necessary. Financial information is used to bill the customer for products. You also have the option of ordering products over the telephone and you may choose to pay by check, credit card or money order. If you provide your phone number and order, we may send you text messages in the future. However, the text messages are not spam. They are used solely to make certain relevant announcements. You can opt-out of receiving text messages.

**Use of Information**

Information collected by The Six Figure Program is used for the following purposes: We collect information to process customer orders, to contact our customers concerning the status of an order or to answer any of their questions. We collect information to contact users about upcoming Six Figure Program sales, promotions, product information, and to participate in contests. Your information may be shared with carefully selected third party partners and may be used by them to inform you of offers, promotions and services from these organizations which may be of interest to you. The Six Figure Program will have access to and will use the personally identifiable information you provide in connection with your purchases on this Website, and it may use your data for payment processing and authorization, fraud protection and credit risk reduction, website evaluation and data analysis, and also for marketing and promotional material distribution for the Six Figure Program family of companies. We may share personal information with our Website hosting partners, and other parties who assist us in operating our Website or conducting Six Figure Program business, so long as those outside parties agree to keep the information confidential. We may release your personal information to comply with the law, to enforce our Website policies, or to protect our or others' rights, property, or safety. We do not sell any information about our users on the individual customer level. As with any business, it is possible that as our business develops, we might sell or buy online stores or other assets. In such transactions, information about customers often is among the transferred assets. Accordingly, in the unlikely event that our company or substantially all of our assets are acquired by a third party, such information may be one of the transferred assets.

**Updating of Information**

In order to change or modify information previously provided by you, please choose "My Account" and update your information using the options on this page.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make any material changes in the way we collect, use, and/or share your personal information, we will notify you by sending you an e-mail at the last e-mail address that you provided us, and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on the Website covered by this Privacy Policy. Any material changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective upon the earlier of thirty (30) calendar days following our transmittal of an e-mail notice to you or thirty (30) calendar days following our posting of the notice of changes on the Website covered by the Privacy Policy. Please note that, at all times, you are responsible for updating your personal information to provide us your current e-mail address. In the event that the last e-mail address that you have provided us is not valid, or for any other reason is not capable of delivering to you the notice described above, our transmittal of the e-mail containing such notice will nevertheless constitute effective notice of the changes described in the notice. In any event, changes to this Privacy Policy may affect our use of personal information that you provided us prior to our notification to you of the changes. If you do not wish to permit changes in our use of your information, you must notify us prior to the effective date of the changes that you wish to deactivate your account with us.

**Cookies**

The Six Figure Program does place a feature called a "cookie" on your hard drive. A cookie is a small data file that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie may contain certain information, such as a unique user session ID number, which is used to track the page(s) you visited. This unique number allows us to keep track of your order as you shop on our site. Cookies also allow us to recognize registered users when they visit, and to provide those customers with specific related information. If you register with us or order from our Website, we use cookies to monitor and maintain information about how you use our Website and what you buy. If you do not register or buy from the site, we may monitor and maintain information about your use of our Website in order to improve your shopping experience. Our Website logs do generate certain kinds of non-identifying site usage data, such as the number of visits to our Website and pages viewed. This information is used for internal purposes by technical support staff to provide better service to you. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change the configuration of your browser to prevent this from occurring. Even without a cookie, you can still take advantage of most of the features of our Website, including making a purchase, but we will not be able to recognize you as a registered user unless you log-in.

**Contact Information**

Six Figure Program  
1608 S. Ashland Ave # 17763  
Chicago, IL 60608

**Phone**

1-800-497-5331

**Email**

dave@sixfigureprogram.com  
ben@sixfigureprogram.com
